manulife investment management is proud
to introduce
manulife ifunds a new digital fund
investment platform
for you to seamlessly open a new account
invest in funds and manage your
portfolio
anytime anywhere swap
tedious paper forms for a holistic and
time-saving digital experience
with your smartphone tablet
laptop or desktop
with insights from our professional
advisors
and data from the comprehensive tools in
manulife iphones
explore our diverse range of unit trust
funds
as you build up your investment
portfolio
with a helicopter view key tabs on your
portfolio at a glance
with the option to drill down to each
fund for more information
switch funds when required to adapt to
market opportunities
and your investment objectives it is
convenience
made available right at your fingertips
what are you waiting for come on board
with manulife iphones now
to learn more reach out to your manulife
investment management advisor
or contact our customer service now at
zero three
two seven one nine nine two seven one
you